Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/roancaitlin (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Education

Nursing

Nursing Documentation

Certifications

ACLS - current

NIH Stroke Scale certification - current

American Heart Association BLS/ CPR certified - current

ALS - current

Honors-Awards

Dean's List

Roan Razon

Travel RN

Norfolk, Virginia

Summary

Travel RN with 3.5 years acute care clinical experience. IMU/ PCU/stepdown, Med/Surg, telemetry, stroke, cardiac, limited ED experience, float pool experience. ACLS/BLS certified.

Direct Commissioned Officer in the US Navy Reserve Nurse Corps.

I'm a hard worker and strive to become a better version of myself while serving others.

Experience

Aya Healthcare

Travel RN

November 2018 - Present (1 year 8 months)

U.S. Navy Reserve

LTJG

September 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Navy Nurse Corps

Sentara Healthcare

Registered Nurse

October 2016 - December 2018 (2 years 3 months)

Norfolk, Virginia

VCU Health System

Care Partner

December 2014 - June 2016 (1 year 7 months)

Richmond, VA

- Assisted nurses in providing effective patient care via communication and completing delegated tasks i.e. vital checks
- Assisted patients in daily AM care, performing ADLs
- Ensured patient safety by rounding hourly on patients, maintaining therapeutic communication, and documenting patient information

Page 1 of 2

- Operated EKG machines, glucometers, bladder scanners
- Performed phlebotomy (blood draws and IV starts) when needed
- Performed clerical duties as Unit Secretary

Childtime Learning Center
Teacher Assistant
June 2014 - August 2014 (3 months)
Va Beach, VA

- Ensured the daily care of children from infancy to school age
- Maintained a fun and interactive classroom that is clean and organized

Coast Guard Exchange Cashier Checker May 2012 - August 2012 (4 months) Chesapeake, VA

• Operated cash register, maintained records of sales, turned in sales records/ money/customer checks/charge slips at the end of shift, provided information concerning availability of goods sold/prices/condition of merchandise, kept records of customer traffic during the day, insured that proper stock level is maintained, cleaned counters of serving area.

Education

Virginia Commonwealth University
Bachelor's Degree, Bachelor of Science, Nursing and
Psychology · (2010 - 2016)

Tallwood High School High School, International/Global Studies · (2006 - 2010)